Hi welcome back.
Have you been looking for that perfect brunette hair color?
Well today I'm going to show you how to get it.
Today is the day that you can be the brunette that you want to be.
Now listen colors sometimes can be easy to do and sometimes they can be difficult but I'm going to give you a few tips that can help you achieve the color that you want.
Now color is on a color level, 1 through 10, brown being a 4 or 5.
Now if you want to achieve a rich brown, stay on your level, something in a 3 or a 4.
If you have a light skin tone you might want to go with a lighter brown.
If you have a medium skin tone you might want to go with like an auburn brown to add some richness.
If you have a dark skin tone like myself you might want to go for a very very rich brown.
Now listen if you can't find the color that you're looking for ask your professional stylist.
Go in, chat it up, and get the information that you need to go home and achieve the color that you want.
My name is Sylvia Russell and I hope that you find the perfect brunette for your hair color.